It's all sorted out.
Um...
I'm still thinking about it
What are you thinking?
Right to Korea
Weren't you coming in?
It's because I need a plan
This summer
It had to be different.
Last summer, the rainy season was a bit long.
Because the sky is gloomy
I couldn't see any stars at all
The hottest of my life
It was a boring summer
This is it
The 100th war with Song Ha-kyung
Is it because I couldn’t finish it?
In your name
Do you want me to do it? Right now?
No, soon Song Ha-kyung
I'm going to ask you to hand over the power of attorney.
do it after that
Please upload this as a file
Ha-kyung
Are you afraid of selling the peanut shop?
If my dad doesn't give me a power of attorney, I can do it.
Then you have to fight with dad.
That's right, only Song Ha-kyung is having a harder time.
The only adults left around are
It's just my dad
fight with dad
How does he feel?
He has to fight me, he
Hey, I've been in this neighborhood for 17 years.
Teachers will definitely do it too.
June in Seoul
Still warming up
You can do it!
This year
I might be a little hotter than summer
But by July
The summer in Patan-myeon is going to be pretty wild too.
We have no choice but to prepare more carefully.
Maybe something unexpected happened
Even if I wake up
It's okay
As far as getting hurt
Because I came prepared
Baek Do-young is dead
That too a year ago
Right?
Why have you been treating me all this time?
Are you pretending to be Baek Doyoung?
Why?
Why did you pretend to be Baek Doyoung to me all this time?
Write letters and send emails
Why did you even call me, why!
“Daeungjeon”
How could you do this to me?
Say something, Baek Do-ha.
Say something!
At least make an excuse!
No one gets hurt
The result of my efforts to do this
Because it was just this
Let's never see each other again
So you hate me
during this summer
Because you'll like it
Song Ha-kyung and my 100th war
It's finally started properly
What?
There's only me
Song Ha-kyung Is there anyone in my life that I will hate?
Because now I'm the only one left
So feel free to hate me
next to me
me too
Because I'll do whatever I want
Does that mean you like me?
You do whatever you want
I do whatever I want
Let's hold on like that, let's
crazy guy
Crazy guy is better
Rather than someone who regrets all day long
doing nothing
Just waiting
The last two years are enough
Would you like to watch it together?
'Subak has a lot of tears.
Wash your face often...'
Hey, watermelon
Where has your mom gone?
It's not even July
The weather has already become violent.
And in the end
Song Ha-kyung left the peanut restaurant.
I have something to tell you.
Are you kidding?
Last time to the mayor
Because I want to look good
Leave that mess behind
You want to quit now?
That, Cheontan Senior Center
Welfare Center for the Disabled
How many years have they both been together?
It's not being completed.
I will take care of that.
Jumugwan Song, who likes to hang out as much as possible
I put it in the right spot.
Now what kind of whim is this?
Even if you don’t come up with a concept like this
Because I won't cut it
- Please stop...
- No!
I'm serious, please cut me out.
Mr. Song Ha-kyung
Oh, what now...
Yes, this is Manager Jeon Ye-eun.
Ah, yes
Oh, okay, yes.
Don't talk nonsense, just follow me
Because it's a special call from the mayor.
- Hello, Mayor.
- Now, sit down here.
hello
What are you doing, Director Song?
yes
Director Baek won the Seoul Architecture Award.
Received the construction award
Director Song is a graduate of Patan High School.
I am very excited
If the two of you collaborate
What kind of synergy will arise, hahaha?
Patan-myeon, Pacheon-si
The only high school closed
It was also featured a lot in the news.
Public opinion and media without noise
Don't miss it all
Please make it well, okay?
Come to think of it
The month after completion
Re-election, Mr. Mayor.
If you win the construction award before re-election,
I think it would be perfect
Wow, this is too much
I'm looking forward to it.
Anyway, I hope everyone
To Director Baek Do-ha
Please give me strength, yes?
strength!
strength
Do you think things are not going well?
I thought you said you would quit
Did things not go well?
It's been 3 days
Clothes and whatever else you need
Take care of it for me?
I left my tablet behind too.
Dew went home, right?
You should know...
- Uh, Director Song?
- Hello
Baek Do-ha
As you can see here
It's a public place
Please show some respect.
The green space ratio...
Create a long green space
Although the ratio seems small
Pacheon building ordinance standards
It was correct.
The movement of tourists and employees
They should be separated
Ah, that's in the implementation design book.
I'm here
I just sent you the file again
Would you like to see the elevation drawing?
That way you won't get anything
But this budget
Design cost higher than average
It's set a little low.
그 부분에 관해선 제가
I'll contact you again later
Hey, Song Ha-kyung
You're sick of me now
We have to work face to face
So are my feelings real or not?
Don't start a fight
Let's be fair and stick together
Ha, he must be crazy, really.
Hey Song, how much did you drink?
- 슬
- What's going on?
The guy who quit drinking for a year
Hey, you stop drinking.
- Oh, stop drinking, you Jinsang!
- iced coffee!
- hey!
- Oh, really!
Oh, really come to your senses.
- Hey
- Take off your shoes, shoes.
America's water
One day of puppy pranks
why am i like this
- Are you agitated, huh?
- Ugh! Wow, Mr.
That bastard has lawsuits and lawsuits
It all seems like a simple joke
Even if I go back
The only thing left will be me again
Work and home are all a mess right now.
Ah...
Don't start a fight
Let's be fair and square.
Fair and square
No!
no
Hey, Song Ha-kyung
Why are you because of that bastard?
Are you leaving Bari?
fish oil, seeds
Hey, why are you
- Oh, don't do it, don't do it.
-Why 12 billion?
Give up on the project?
If that bastard gives up
Something comfortable, huh?
Hey, don't throw things like this.
- I
- Wow...
I'll show you my territoriality
Oh, the bag
Why are you throwing it, really?
you
It'll pop up soon, you hottie.
You bastard!
ah! Ah, ah...
Oh, it hurts
Ah, sad, it hurts
What is this?
um
Our village leaders
As you can see now
A novice architect opened our alma mater
I'm trying to change it like this
Our village leaders
You have such a great love for children.
Even if I don’t say anything else
Of course you will be against it.
Just in case
This is how we served you
Oh, by the way, Director Song
We eat out all the time in Patan.
Ah, my mother-in-law’s kimchi stew again.
You guys like it, right?
It's delicious
Now, let's eat
Shall we try it deliciously?
Eat, eat, it's getting cold, it's getting cold
Ha...
Ah, I think it's genius.
Why is this genius going crazy?
I'll let you go
Just wait
Hey Taeyoung, panelists.
I think we need to spread it out a bit.
This way?
Oh, first of all, the surrounding commercial districts
The colors don't match
try making it again
Shhh
Ah, yes, Director Song.
I was already going to call you, but
Resident briefing session
Got a date
It's tomorrow, are you available?
The faster the better
Yes, thank you, see you tomorrow.
What is it?
Brother, I sent you before
Do you have a resident briefing session plan file?
Try launching it quickly
Oh my... can you really do that?
Hey, Major Baek
Oh, if you're going to do it, you have to do it right.
Without regrets
Yes? Where?
What is this all about?
I'm going to finish it in one go.
Yes?
Ah, Director Song Ha-kyung.
Re-planning your budget
It must be a pain in the ass.
all week long
A painfully planned schedule
I'll finish it in one day
I
ah, ah
Yes, hello, hello
Hello!
Our women’s club sisters
Resident association brothers
And the presidents of our merchant association
-What day is today?
- The day to make two dog wine!
Ah, if you think about it this way
It's a village festival.
At our women’s president’s house
They say they do it by gathering together like this.
I need a parasol like this
I tried installing it
Yes, mothers
Take off the calyx and throw it aside.
It's okay to leave the surgery alone
- Yes
- You're good.
Wait, this isn't it.
why am i here
Are you picking the calyx?
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot!
It's nice because it's spacious, but the problem is that it's hot.
Oh my, what should I do?
Is our women’s president hot?
You can just use this
Wow, cool
I have a drink each
I'll bring it to you
- I'm hot too.
- Yes
Me too!
It has to dry out
This place
Now, take a drink of this one at a time.
- Wow, thank you.
- Yes, good luck.
I don't have anything but mine
Oh, I'll get it for you.
Hey, it's a hot day, but our Dr. Song
You need to say something refreshingly.
- Me?
- Yes
uh
Applause!
Uh, yes
You are currently refining
These azalea petals
Our Patan-myeon’s unique liquor?
Two-dog owner
It will be used to make dugyeonju.
Every year at the women’s association,
With the residents like this
Removing the calyx of this azalea flower
I'm holding an event.
How are you all enjoying it?
yes!
Ah, Director Song.
Azalea flowers in Patan-myeon
They say it grows a lot.
How many flowers will there be in total?
A thousand flowers?
Well, if I guess
Probably about a million flowers, right?
Wow, it's really blooming a lot.
My favorite K-pop
‘A Million Roses’
'A million roses'
Then give it a try!
call me
Call me! Call me!
Oh, this person is an architect.
Tell me what song to sing, no
- Ouch!
- Call me!
Chairman, no!
♪ Long ago, on a star ♪
♪ When I come out into the world ♪
Oh my
You sing so well
♪ Give love and come ♪
♪ I heard a small voice ♪
Oh my, it's good
♪ hating, hating
Without any hate ♪
Cool!
All together!
♪ Generously, generously
When you just give love ♪
♪ A million flowers, a million flowers
A million flowers are blooming ♪
♪ Nostalgic and beautiful
I can go to my starland ♪
Applause!
- Ugh
-Why is it like that?
Ah, Vice President
Don't make me sing or anything like that.
I guess it really turned
- Thank you always.
- Take care of it
Ah, our director Baek
It was originally like that... but
- I'm so excited today.
- I'll go.
- You were a little embarrassed, right?
- It's okay.
- Because the next stage is real.
- So,
Where's next? Let's go
But just looking at this
There are no trees
originally at school
There are dense evergreen trees.
Ah, old man, that
Next to the original observatory
I don't keep trees.
Because it interferes with observation
before construction
I'm trying to transplant it.
What is it?
Uprooting trees at school?
Why did you pick it? why?
Don't you know your broken spirit? Destroyed!
♪ Evergreen trees that are green all year round ♪
♪ Pathan's
It's like my heart ♪
♪ Round sky and round town ♪
♪ We live together in the mountains and valleys ♪
Zero difference!
♪ Ah, ruin ♪
♪ Eternal Cradle ♪
♪ Let’s embrace the clear spirit ♪
♪ We are Patan High School... ♪
Anyway
This is a school with this spirit.
How many riders do you have?
Don't you know that either?
Oh, I don't think that's...
What about the director, aren’t you from Pacheon?
Huh?
Not Korean, but American.
child
Let alone those from Pathan High School.
Unless you are from Pacheon City
It won't be easy
Partners, construction companies
They must all be Pacheon natives.
How are you going to communicate?
I can't do it, I can't do it! No way!
No, instead of blood in the veins
I also have two dogs and soybean noodles flowing.
I can't touch Patango, it won't work.
- No!
- cancer!
I've already met with the companies.
And the elderly
I also eat bean noodles every day.
No triangles!
The sky has been round since ancient times, right?
The square thing is land, right? huh?
So our Patan-myeon is
Surrounded by mountains
The terrain is round, the houses are square
So heaven and earth are in good harmony
It's that kind of town, that's what I'm saying
But here...
Are you going to build something square?
nice!
game over
Goodbye, Baek Do-ha
Ah, Mr. Go.
If you've seen this plan, you'll know.
The building itself is not triangular.
Only internally...
Ah!
Boy, I don't understand what you're saying.
- Stop disbanding, go, go, everyone.
- Yes.
It's useless nonsense
What do you mean...
Ai, Director Song
What are you doing?
If your name is from Patan-myeon,
I should have stopped you a long time ago.
- Sorry!
- Dr. Song disapoint
Wait!
Hold on
Elderly people
before coming here
I came to see the women’s president.
I especially
I'm taking care of you
Patan-myeon is
Dugyeonju made from this azalea
It's the most famous
Ah, this, this is a dog breed
Isn't it a special edition?
The women’s president too
They only take it out on holidays
Received on Danot Day
Made only with spring water
Just one drink
You can feel the spring in Patan-myeon
That drink!
No, this, this must be fake.
Ah, people from Seoul, no.
There is no way an American could have saved this
Ah, indeed
You'll know if it's real or not when you taste it.
Is it real?
- Huh?
- really?
- Really, really?
- Yes
I have a few more bottles, so sit down and take your time
Would you like to talk about Patan High School?
Draw, get a cup.
- Chief? Lee, Chief
- Take a glass, glass, glass.
No...
- Chief
- Chief, sit down.
Let's talk slowly
Oh, you can't do this, really.
Just wait like this...
Oh, let's go
Ta-da, me too
Eating too much
No?
What are you two?
What exactly is Chairman?
Why those precious dogs?
Did you stab that Chief Baek?
Dr. Song said during the flood
Don’t you know that even azaleas were in an uproar?
At most, everything that was dried was wet.
Then I went to the northernmost part of Gangwon-do and
It was that bachelor who picked the azaleas for me.
If it wasn't for that, there wouldn't be today's event.
Thank you
Now
Now, for the ruin.
For!
Now, now
good
Hey, seniors
You've probably seen it a lot already.
The summer triangle is really bright, right?
In the past, when I was looking for a way
They said they found this constellation.
Uh, right
Navigator’s navigation chart
I did it and did it
That's right, in Seoul
In this town less than an hour away
If you can come see the constellations
It would be great for tourism as well.
Just...
Huh?
If you look closely, Jicheol is your friend, huh?
He's the son of the Baek director, right?
- Yes
- Oh, I see.
I heard you'll become a star doctor
He climbed the mountain every night
Aren’t you a troublemaker?
That's right
I haven't been able to see it lately
Well, I'm your younger brother.
Now you can see it often
I live at the peanut restaurant in front of here.
child
Then we are Patan residents.
- Yes
- how
Are you going to give me permission and throw it away?
Village history
How do you decide when to drink alcohol?
People really...
That's right
Well, you
Studying about this breakdown
I know you did a lot, I get it.
What's important? huh? huh?
This is the heart of the residents.
you in this town
Even just one person on your side
Did you make it right? huh?
Agggg!
If you're going to ruin it like this, just go ahead and do it.
Why don't you play with the village leaders? Hey, hey
Boy, what I ruined
I will eat it
Okay, that's it.
Your mom was like that too
They say that if you mess up, you always eat it.
Hehe, still
I was really good at picking flowers.
Every spring your mother
I picked the most azaleas.
I remember, I'm still at home
3 bottles of Dugyeonju
My mom fell into a coma when I got married.
They said they had pre-soaked it for you to take away.
I helped you with that too
Your mom is such a sucker for food.
But I measured my hands again
Picking azaleas, GoStop, playing Yut
I was really good at this
So, I hope to catch that too.
I learned everything from my mom
Back when my mom was alive
I never miss a village event
It's been a while since you looked like this, it's nice
What are you doing, Song Ha-kyung?
Why are you talking about your mom here?
Why did you throw a slash and burn attack and fall asleep now?
Let's decide this
Oh, what about the village?
Oh my, Chairman.
Anyway, this is
Too bad for Americans...
call
Huh?
instead
Come take my side
Can I do it?
Director
Stop eating that ruined slash-and-burn rice
Team up with me
Yes?
Director
You're good at that, right?
It's a hit
Come on!
So now
Yutnori: Approval of the observatory or not?
Are you making a decision?
That's right, that's right
No, rather, I
Why am I with Director Baek?
We're on the same side, aren't you, village leaders?
to
Director Song, are you not confident? Are you scared?
Oh, how can I
I stick with the village leaders, really!
No, and the village
How can you play Yut... really?
let's just do it
Oh, just try it.
Do it, do it, do it
Okay, let's do it.
- How about it, huh?
- This person called.
No, I can't do this.
It doesn't make sense, it doesn't make sense.
Now, Dr. Song, let’s go!
Wait a minute, try it.
Okay, that's it, look up.
There is also a plan to tear down this wall.
Huh?
The late chief said so.
If you don’t play Yut sincerely,
Agreement to tear down the fence
I'm going to pretend it never happened
- No...
- Hey, let's play.
Come on, let's go
Yut!
Well done our Chief God!
Hahahaha!
Dog, dog! fold!
Hey, Yutnori is so fun!
Vice president, dog
- Do, one, two
- Do, dog
That's right, haha!
Dr. Song's mother
Wasn’t she the goddess of Yutnori?
‘Mo!’, then Mo comes out.
‘It’s Yut!’ Then Yut appears, huh?
However, Dr. Song
You were kind to me, kind of to me.
Oh my!
in heaven
Our sister-in-law is crying!
The yutnori champion of yesteryear looked like this
I'm leaving!
It's our turn, right? Please give it to me
- Oh, draw it.
- I have to give it to you.
Hey, rubber band
Yeah
Oh my, what should I do?
Our Dr. Song
Looks like it's going to hit well
child
I tried sincerely.
From now on, I have to do mo, yut, mo.
catch up with us
There's no way I can win today
Village leaders
I lost the game
Can you handle it?
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute
I lost the game
Can you handle it?
Ah, c, ah, really, c.
Wow! Won!
after
- uh?
- huh?
I'm collecting it.
- Mo, moda, uh
- This
Isn’t this a foul? uh?
This almost came out a hundred times.
If it comes out in 100, it comes out right away.
Why would I use a foul?
Let's go
Huh? Uh...
Come on!
- Please, please, please, please
- Brother, you can just be a dog, dog.
Chief Joe
Apply nose oil
Huh?
- It's white!
- Baekdo...
It’s white! hey!
Well, it's okay!
- It's our turn, right? yes
- It's okay!
do well
Really please, really please
Huh?
Oh, moda, moda!
-Moda, moda!
- Moda! Hahaha, Moda!
- I won, I won, I won.
- Moda!
- Hey!
- Boy...
Oh my, that, that...
Ah, sir...
I'm finally back
I knew
That Song Ha-kyung
very briefly
I have become the old me
Because of Baek Do-ha
What are you really doing?
Let's go, you go home
Are you going to go get your tablet?
You have to hurry, the car is cut off
Come quickly
Dr. Song's Resurrection
It's been a while, huh?
Still love the elders
I'm receiving it in abundance
What are you really?
all day today
What are you thinking?
Director Song
It was Director Song who came up with this plan.
Participate in Yutnori
You win in the end
I also received the consent of the village leaders.
Director Song, is this you?
It’s been a while since Song Ha-kyung had fun
I liked watching you play
To deal with Song Ha-kyung
I need to prepare like this
Very reassuring
I came back prepared
‘I only come here during summer vacation anyway.
'The guy who passed away without even completing a month'
‘It’ll be an empty check this time too.
It's obvious, well'
You thought so, right?
'In the end, the whitewashing
'I will definitely lose to Song Ha-kyung'
You thought so, you
I'm sorry again and again
why are you like that
Do you want to stick with me?
Do you want to be away from me?
you
If you keep acting awkwardly in front of me
I keep remembering something I forgot
I've barely been able to hold it in
I've lived well without you
- But after you appeared...
- It's hard?
When you look at me, do you think of Baek Doyoung?
When the three of us were together
Are you having a hard time because you keep thinking about it?
You too
It's hard for you too when you look at me
If you see me too
Don’t you think of Baek Doyoung?
no
When I see you
I remember the days when I liked you
And then
I can't say properly that I like it
I remember myself coming back
The photo was taken by my brother.
Sent to you in the name of Baek Doyoung
I wrote the email but
The photo was taken by my brother, right?
expedition people
Among the items sent
There was a camera
It was full of pictures of constellations.
especially
summer triangle
Now it's up to you
I guess talking about Baek Do-young is easy.
when you come back
I decided to only think about myself
Things I did while thinking about you
I won't do it anymore
What?
Then, I pretended to be Baek Doyoung.
Are you saying it's all because of me?
The lady was suffering from illness the whole time.
You were a mess the whole time nursing the sick.
My brother
was missing
I wish my brother was alive too
It's a lie that I started hoping for
It'll be better for you and me
- That's how it started...
- So
You're broken because of me too.
Oh, it was unfortunate
I tried not to hurt anyone
Because it was a method, but...
So
That lie
You did it because of me.
Baekdoha
Do you understand now?
We always treat each other like this
It only makes me make bad choices
Wow
It's been a while for me today
I brought up my mom’s story.
While making two dog wine
I'm talking about my mom
He did it casually
But I can't do that
There is such a thing as ‘what if’, Seul-ah.
If only I had left City Hall early that day.
Without chewing on mom’s phone
I wish I received it right away
Don't miss the bus dispatch
If I got on it right away
That ‘what if’
If I didn't live in a peanut house
So, if I didn't meet the thieves
Think like that, endlessly
liked you
I remember those days
And then
I can't say properly that I like it
I remember myself coming back
What about you?
When you look at me too
The summer you liked me
Doesn’t that remind you?
so because of that
Don't you feel sorry for Baek Do-young?
I told Baek Doyoung
If you hadn't told me you liked Baek Do-ha
If you didn't say it
if
Are you withdrawing the cow?
Yes, to Baek Do-ha.
I'll hand over the whole house.
Are you serious?
Are you handing over all rights to me?
yes
According to my share
I will only accept 50%
It's a prefabricated wooden house.
I even suffered from flood damage.
50% of the total appraised value
Does that make sense?
Then I get feelings.
I will comply as is.
Repair costs due to flooding
If you claim, you pay separately.
Well then, let’s go.
Talk to me for a moment
You can give up the peanut shop?
Yeah
I don't want to fight with you anymore
I just did that in the first place
It was okay if I didn't make it.
I guess I was a little childish
I keep fighting with you at the peanut restaurant.
I don't want to do that
Without even thinking about you
And then
I keep going back to those days
- So why is that?
- I don't want to do that.
I blame you
i continue
I want to live the way I used to live
without you
"Pluto Atelier"
Ha...
What you asked for earlier
An ash tree sapling that resembles Jongman.
These are stores where you can get it.
I organized it in detail without leaving anything out.
In the future, something like this
There will be no contact
Ha...
- Hey, Baek Doyoung
- Uh, song.
Oh, she said the surgery went well.
Thank goodness
Uh, I really wanted to go this time.
Well, it just so happens that next week
Climbing Mount Denali was planned.
It's the highest mountain in North America
“Baekdoha”
Are you cool?
After
Get on first
Where are you going? just say it here
Ah, the car behind is roaring.
Can't you see? Ride fast
seat belt
To me
This was the most difficult?
Because it wasn’t the method I used.
Until this is completed
Because they couldn't find a technician
In the end I shaved it off
So
There is also a medal here
Injector until completion date
I think I got hit about five times.
But I kept it in the end
- All of this took less than half a year.
- So?
What do you want to say?
What have you been doing for hours?
Song Ha-kyung
I'm telling you now
I'm going to throw my last hand
I did this
I didn't know you were going to throw it already.
Coming to you this summer
‘I shouldn’t use this’
‘Please don’t throw this away’
I came like this
This is not July or August
They throw it in June
I guess I'm still far away
To beat Song Ha-kyung
But me too
I brought the card of conversion
August 31st
It's our completion date.
Just live with me until then, okay?
Until the end of this summer
If you can't hold on like that,
At that time, I will really get out of front of you.
What's with me
If it's still a pain for you
I'll leave after it's completed, okay?
So stop pushing me away
come back home
If you're not with me this summer
doesn't mean anything to me
time to think
I need it
Welcome
If only I had
They say your summer is unlucky
Then a little more
It's okay even if you're unlucky
Because it's summer
Boss, here
With a bottle of sake
Katsudon Hanayo
Are you a stalker?
Last time he came to my house, but this time...
No, this is not Pacheon.
In Seoul, a city with a population of 10 million,
We just ran into each other
To pretend it was a coincidence
You’re not doing it, are you?
thank you
-You ordered what you always eat.
- Yes
Are you leaving work early today?
- Boss, with a bottle of sake.
- Here's a bottle of sake.
- 4 skewers
-Yeomtong skewers 4...
Ah, what should I do with this?
There are only 5 flames left now.
I'll give you 4, then
I also have 4
um
Are you eating pork cutlet and rice together?
What is this?
Isn’t this how everyone eats?
Tonkatsu and rice like Song Ha-kyung
A person who eats at once
I got used to eating alone
That's it
Take the pork cutlet and eat it
Because there is no one
I started with pork cutlet
In contrast to eating
That's right, 4 sons and 1 daughter.
To my brother and sister
You grew up getting hit, right?
Attorney, I only handle appeals.
That's a problem solver or something like that.
They said no
yes
As a bastard, I am ranked low.
The first trial is all up to the brothers.
Song Ha-kyung said that the funds
You are in a situation where you are lacking a lot.
I’m sick of tiki-taka too.
Let's just be salty, salty people
But Song Ha-kyung
why so
Do you want to come up to Seoul?
What is good?
Seoul is full of good things.
All with smartphones
Like this, crackling
Many people live alone
I have no interest in the person next to me
How good is it? one star
Even without it, it’s deep. I like it.
Why are there no stars?
Seoul is truly a paradise.
Seoul night view
You've never seen it properly, right?
Instead of stars here
I see people
Drunk people, people tired from work
These are all violations of employment and labor laws
This is a night view I created.
The garbage truck will be here soon.
What is this?
Ah, this
It's the secret to a 99% win rate.
Keywords found by digging into the original defendant
Write it down on this bingo board.
If it's one bingo, there's no chance of winning.
Two Bingo Myeon Soso
Three bingo is a perfect win
Ordinary people are ordinary
Because it is organized in these nine spaces
Then in the center of my bingo board
What did you write?
first written down
What is your cheat key?
Why am I telling you that?
To the enemy
I'm not filing a lawsuit.
Well then, would you like to have a fight?
Hey, song
What is it?
What, really, where has he gone?
I can't connect
After the beep...
Hey Baekdoha, where are you?
house
What are you doing?
Ha-kyung didn’t even come home.
Oh, all day today
They don't even answer the phone
What are you really thinking?
Oh, aren’t you worried about Song Ha-kyung?
Did you write that I am a bastard?
It was written in modern terms as ‘out of wedlock’.
The brothers are also the poop wipers.
Can I circle it?
No, a bastard is born out of wedlock.
Write it down and write it down
Why is a poop wipe called a poop wipe?
I'll write you as an appellate expert.
That's it, let's move on, it's my turn
My mom's cancer
Did you write that he passed away?
Sure
It's your death anniversary soon.
My father said he couldn't take care of me.
You ran away to Thailand, right?
What, why are you avoiding one hit and two?
No way, lawyer
Is it Three Bingo already?
No, two bingo, the middle is still there
child in the middle
What did you write?
Baekdoha? Or a peanut restaurant?
With Baek Do-ha
Are you finished talking well?
It wasn't long, but two people
So much so that they even filed a lawsuit against that house.
I think we have a lot to talk about.
Oh, and last time
There's more I couldn't tell you.
Why did you take on the peanut restaurant case?
I said I could lose the case.
Always doing everything to win
Because all we do is fight
It was refreshing to receive such a request.
Just drag it out for the summer
Because I can lose the case
That was Baek Do-ha's condition.
bingo game today
Very useful and hit the nail on the head
Without even knowing much
I was rude a lot.
You don’t know?
petition, direct argument
Final argument and proof of contents
I know it well after reading it dozens of times.
Besides, I heard a secret today.
Seup
Oh, wait a minute.
Is it okay if I don’t take it?
I've been getting chat messages since a while ago.
Ah, well, even if you don’t see it anyway
It works, yeah
Ah, Mr.
Hey, lawyer, I'm sorry.
I think I should go first.
Come in quickly
Song Ha-kyung
Uh, hey, what is it?
What, what kind of blackout?
you toad house
Are you sure you checked it properly?
uh, now
Me, on the basement floor
That one was varnished.
Rather, you now
Are you in the right mind to do this? uh?
Is it going to hurt anything?
Oh, right, hey, ah...
Ha...
Huh? Where did you go?
I'm surprised
Are you looking for the two dog wine that the lady made?
Yeah
Are you going to move that to a jar?
no
‘24-hour business trip anywhere’
It was written down.
They say it’s not allowed in Patan-myeon?
Then you shouldn't have exaggerated advertising.
How, to the Consumer Agency
Shall we report it? yes?
Hey...
Ah, when I had a power outage earlier.
You've done it all, so you...
- Give it to me or not?
- A
- Really
- When you have good words to say, give it to me.
Ah, why did you cut your leg...
That's right
Why did you take my phone away...
Ah
Ah, hey, what are we going to do with this?
- uh?
uh?
Hey, I lived this.
Oh!
Mr. Lee
Big~
Hey
- Just take a bite too.
- I don't like it
You go to the women’s council president’s house and get some.
What my mom made
There's only one left
Anyway, mothball, huh? The lady too, huh?
Are you going to ask me to share some?
um
Just give me a bite too
I hate it
Hey, just one bite
- No!
- Baby, just give me one bite.
- Hey, it's mine!
- Oh, just one bite.
Let go!
you did it first
Hey, Baek Do-ha
Oh, it's cold!
wait
Ha-kyung, Ha-kyung!
Ha-kyung, I was wrong, haha!
Ha-kyung!
Ha-kyung?
Song Ha-kyung?
hey!
you, Mr.
Isn’t it amazing?
That's what home is like
Even if you feel like you're dead, you'll come back to life quickly
Hey, Baek Do-ha
You are a truly unlucky person.
When I get married
They tried to take me into a coma
My mom’s two dogs
Don't you want me to drink it all today?
With a guy I don't want to deal with
Like babies in the night
Don't you make me play in the water?
And in the end
In your words
Make me answer like this
yes
Let's try what you said.
- Really?
- instead
your construction date
Don't go over one more day
Ha...
I was really scared this time
Hey, it's summer anyway
It's the season of abandoning me
A fortune that never existed before
I'm stuck with you
Nothing will change
Spending a season with you
Nothing will change for us either
summer is long
The guy who returned after only 21 days
I got 80 days
'Cause I'll do whatever it takes
So properly
I'll try to change your mind
our last summer
It has begun
- What is it?
- Cohabitation contract
In our summer
There were always a lot of unexpected events.
Can't sleep?
You broke into this house
What is the real reason?
I'm just trying to live
With Song Ha-kyung, who hasn't grown up yet
Huh? Huh?
Uhm
Ah, if you look closely
You both look like you haven't grown up yet
This is because of you, you
You, you, because of you, to me
Don't ask any more questions, okay?
Yes, I'm leaving
Mr. Song Ha-kyung
Do you like Baek Doha?
I like it
Baek Do-ha's blueprint is
I know better than Baek Doha.
What did I catch?
Don't be mistaken
Yeah, actually I...